http://www.tecomate.com/content/index.php/privacypolicy

Tecomate Seed Catalog
Follow Us On:
Most recent entries
TECOMATE WHITETAIL NATION TV Series - To Feature One of Biggest Non-Typicals Ever Filmed
Terms of Use
By using Tecomate.com, you are agreeing to any terms and conditions stated and set forth on this website.
Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC reserves the right to add, edit or remove any information stated without notification.
Any changes made will be effective immediately.
If you do not agree with any terms and conditions stated within, you are urged not to use this website.
You, as the user of this website, will assume all risks.
Product Guarantee and Disclaimer
Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC warrants to the extent of the purchase price.
We give no further warranty expressed or implied.
Prices are subject to change without notice.
We do not match any company’s guarantees and/or warrantees that they advertise on television, radio, etc.
Our return policy overrides any and all policies set forth by other companies even if they are the manufacturer and/or supplier of the products.
Product Return Policy
We accept returns for unopened products only.
Shipping charges are not refundable.
Returned and orders refused at delivery will be assessed a 15% restocking fee and our incurred shipping fees.
A refund of the original purchase price, less shipping and restocking fees will be issued once confirmed receipt of product(s) at distributor facility.
For items damaged in shipment, please email .(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address) before returning.
Some of the products we sell are covered by a manufacturer’s warranty and require the damage be documented and/or photographed.
Terms of this guarantee are subject to change with or without notice.
Order Cancellation Policy
All orders are automatically uploaded to our secure merchant processor which incurs fees.
Orders cancelled prior to being processed and shipped will be issued a full refund.
If you cancel your order after it has been processed and shipped, an attempt to redirect the shipment can be made for an $11 fee.
Customers may choose to refuse the order delivery and the shipment will be returned to our shipping/distributor facility.
Shipping charges are not refundable.
Orders refused at delivery will be assessed a 15% restocking fee and our incurred shipping fees.
A refund of the original purchase price, less shipping and restocking fees will be issued once confirmed receipt of product(s) at distributor facility.
Terms of this guarantee are subject to change with or without notice.
Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC reserves the right to cancel or deny any orders for any reason.
If your order is cancelled, you will receive notification via email with an explanation or alternatives (if available).
Some of the reasons/situations an order may be cancelled or denied are:
- Order cannot be processed due to an error in the information provided by the customer (i.e. incorrect shipping address).
- If product is delayed out of our distribution facility or is discontinued.
- Incorrect credit/debit card information was provided (i.e. expiration date or billing address).
Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC may cancel/deny any order if fraudulent activity is suspected and may refuse to process subsequent orders from customers with a previous fraudulent order history.
Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC may also refuse any orders connected with a previous credit card dispute.
Privacy
Tecomate respects each individual's right to personal privacy. Generally, you can browse through our website without providing any personal information. However, periodically you may be asked to provide personal information to access a specific information resource or as part of a request for information. We will collect and use information through our website only in the ways disclosed in this statement.
Information Collection
At Tecomate, personal information means any information that may be used to specifically identify an individual, including, but not limited to, name, e-mail address, physical address, gender, occupation, industry, and other information requested when requested in an on-line form. In general, you can visit the Tecomate website anonymously. However, there are areas of the site that require some personal information to enable secure access or to assist us in providing you with specific information about our solutions and services. When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose behind collecting the data. By providing this information, we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this policy. If you do not approve our use of personal information as it is outlined in this policy, do not submit personal information to Tecomate.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Your personal information is never shared outside of Tecomate without your permission. Inside Tecomate, data is stored on web servers with controlled access.
Collecting Domain Information
Like most commercial websites, Tecomate automatically logs all of the traffic coming to and from our website. Part of this data includes the collection of domain information. This data enables us to become more familiar with customers that visit our site, how often they visit, and what sections of the site are most active. Tecomate uses this information to make informed decisions on improving the information and navigation of our site. Tecomate may disclose aggregate statistics about visitors to our site to other third parties. However, any such disclosure will not include any personally identifiable information from any of our visitors.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Tecomate reserves the right to periodically review and amend this policy. We encourage you to review our policy for changes on a regular basis.
Disclaimer
THE MATERIALS, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU ON THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. Tecomate ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, RELIABILITY OR TIMELINESS OF THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY THIS WEB SITE.
YOU UNDERSTAND AND EXPRESSLY AGREE TO USE THIS WEB SITE AT YOUR SOLE RISK, THAT ANY MATERIAL AND/OR DATA DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE IS AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF SUCH MATERIAL AND/OR DATA.
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH ON THIS WEB SITE, Tecomate DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT AND IT MAKES NO WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION REGARDING THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH Tecomate 'S SERVICES, REGARDING ANY GOODS OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED THROUGH Tecomate 'S SERVICES, REGARDING ANY TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH Tecomate 'S SERVICES OR THAT Tecomate 'S SERVICES WILL MEET ANY USER'S REQUIREMENTS, BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE OR ERROR FREE. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Tecomate WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES OF ANY KIND RESULTING FROM THE USE OF OR THE INABILITY TO USE Tecomate 'S SERVICES, RESULTING FROM ANY GOODS OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH Tecomate 'S SERVICES, RESULTING FROM LOSS OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF A USER'S TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA OR FOR THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLES, EVEN IF Tecomate HAD BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
About Tecomate Wildlife Systems, LLC
How it began...A revolutionary new management strategy...
What was started back in 1993 helped open an exciting new chapter in whitetail management history. Lead by Tecomate, food-plot-based nutritional management was introduced to an eager market and soon the whitetail management scene was literally revolutionized. Managers were introduced to an entirely new strategy that allowed them to take control of management on their property and greatly increase the size and number of their deer in ways never before possible.
Company
About Us
Contact Us
Consulting
Tecomate TV
Terms/Privacy Policy
Shop Tecomate
Tecomate Seed
© Copyright 2006- Tecomate® Wildlife Systems, LLC - Privacy PolicyWebsite Design & Development by Cedar Hills Media & Marketing
